# TOMÁS **MARGIOTTIELLO**

TomasMR99@gmail.com My cellphone: +541133470410 Buenos Aires, Argentina

FRONTEND SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Mi name is Tomás. I am 26 years old and am currently studying information systems engineering at the UTN regional Buenos Aires, taking fifth year courses. Additionally, I complement my knowledge with online courses and self-learning.

I consider myself responsible, capable of working in a team and/or individually, proactive and open to new challenges. My knowledge covers both back-end and front-end development, but I am currently focusing on the latter.

At the moment, I am working as a front-end developer in a multidisciplinary team, using agile methodologies, performing code maintenance and developing new features.

#### Skills

#### Front-end

job.

#### I trained myself through courses and self-study in web development, in addition to the constant challenges in my current

#### Back-end

#### Knowledge of different programming paradigms, design patterns and databases.

#### Language

I studied English at a institute, cultural successfully passing the First Certificate exman in 2017.

## Technologies

ReactJS	npm	Spark
HTML5	Bootstrap	SQL / Transact SQL
Javascript / Typescript	Java 8	Git
CSS / SASS	Maven	C/C++

#### Work experience

### Developer Intern Gilbarco Veeder Root

Jun. 2023 - Aug. 2024

I was a developer/QA intern. Scrum. Python. Automation testing.

#### Junior Front-end developer Global Logic

Aug. 2024 - Today

Development of new features in the front-end team. Code maintenance and test cases. ReactJS. Typescript.

### Education

#### Universidad Tecnológica Nacional **Information Systems Engineering**

2018 - Today

Currently in 5th year with a grade point average of 8,2. I have passed 32/43 subjects with 6 pending

# CoderHouse

ReactJS front-end development

2022

Web Development Course. Final Proyect Javascript Course. Final Proyect ReactJS Course. Final Proyect

#### Villa del Parque English cultural institute British English

2006 - 2017

First Certificate exam - dec 2017 - 168/190 - B2.

# Hobbies

In my free time, I like learning about new technologies, improve my front-end skills and knowledges and research tools and YouTube channels that may be useful and interesting. Also, I love travelling and computer games